# **PRANAV WAGH**

## SUMMARY

Talented professional coach/player. Highly motivated player with full efforts. Offering 10 years of experience in badminton.

\*Trained under coach Vad sir in Thane Academy in 2014.

\*Trained under coach Anup Sridhar in Bangalore 2021-22 who was an former world champion with highest world ranking of 24 achieved in early 2008.

\*Constantly training under coach Chaitanya Naik in Pune Solaris club kothrud.

# EXPERIENCE

# Badminton Player Raigad district winner 2021-2022 - Raigad, india

- · Playing since 12 years old
- · experience of 10 years
- MIT inter university winner in singles and doubles
- Raigad district championship doubles winner 2021-2022

#### Participated

- Yonex Sunrise Maharashtra senior inter district State
   Open Championship Parbhani 2019 (quarter finalist)
- Yonex Sunrise first Maharashtra senior state selection badminton tournament 2022 Nanded
- late Nandu natekar Memorial Yonex Sunrise Maharashtra senior State Open championships Nagpur 2022
- Bai series senior badminton tournament 2021 at Hyderabad ,TS
- Bai series senior badminton tournament 2021 at Chennai ,TN
- Yonex Sunrise all India senior ranking badminton tournament 2020 at Goa
- Yonex Sunrise all India senior ranking badminton tournament 2022 at Bangalore (qualified for main draw)

# EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business Administration, BBA IB 2nd year MIT - ADT UNIVERSITY - PUNE, INDIA



# CONTACT

**Address:** Pune,India,411038 **Phone:** +918888594442

Email: pranaavwaggh@gmail.com

## SKILLS

- · professional coach/player
- · Muscle conditioning
- · Mobility exercises
- · Injury prevention
- · Badminton specific workouts